うっ…
Is it him?!
もしかして
No. It's Mr. Lloyds.
いえ ロイズさんです
Oh...
あぁ
Yes, Barnaby speaking.
はい バーナビーです
I just got a call from the Justice Bureau.
ああ 今 司法局から連絡がきてね
Kriem came out of the coma she's been in
ジェイクの一件以来
ずっと昏睡状態だった
クリームの意識が戻ったそうだ
since the Jake incident.
What?!
えっ
"I'll try my best to be wild," eh?
“ワイルドに頑張ります”っか…
Back then, I still hadn't decided
このころは まだキャラに
迷いが あるなあ
what kind of Hero I wanted to be.
Damn!
This isn't the time to be doing this!
だあっ！
こんなことしてる場合じゃねえや
Here! This is for you to remember our promise!
これっ 約束のしるし
All right!
よしっ
yabureta PAGE wa ubawaretanda yo
That torn page was stolen,
破れたページは
奪われたんだよ
dokoka de otoshita oboe wa nai kara
since I don't remember ever dropping it anywhere.
何処かで落とした
覚えはないから
iwakan mo nai hodo kirei ni nai soko ni wa
In the place where the page used to be,
違和感もないほど
綺麗にないそこには
yume to iu nano shou ga tashikani atta
there was a chapter entitled "Dreams."
夢という名の章が確かにあった
nani wo nikumeba ii? kako ka jibun jishin ka
But who should I blame? The past? Myself?
何を憎めばいい
過去か自分自身か
dekireba hoka no dareka de are
If possible, I hope it's someone else.
出来れば他の誰かであれ
monogatari no bokura ga sono mirai wo omou no wa
We, the characters in the story, think of the future.
物語の僕らが
その未来想うのは
nakushita ato demo shuyaku wa kawarenai kara
Because even after we're gone, the main character can't change.
失くした後でも
主役は変われないから
shousan nante sarenakutatte tashikana kyou ga aru nara
Even if I'm not praised, as long as today is here,
賞賛なんてされなくたって
確かな今日があるなら
yume nante namae no shou wa ikura demo tsukurerunda
I can make as many chapters as I want entitled "Dreams."
夢なんて名前の章は
いくらでも創れるんだ
バニー
お前に聞いてほしいことがある
Bunny... There's something I want to tell you.
俺 ワイルドタイガーは諸事情により
Due to certain circumstances, I, Wild Tiger,
have decided to retire from the Hero business.
ヒーローを引退する
よしっ！　これでいくか
All right. I'll go with that line.
Wait... I wonder if Bunny is going to ask me
あっ 諸事情ってとこ
突っ込んでくるかな バニー
what my circumstances are?
おっ
ははははっ
あっ！
Mr. Tiger! You're back!
タイガーさん
帰ってきてたんですか？
Yeah.
おー
もぉ 急に休むから心配してたのよお
Jeez...
You took time off so suddenly. We were all worried about you.
いやあ わりい
Oh, sorry.
たった数日だけど
なんか変な感じだったよね
It was only a few days,
but something didn't feel right about it, didn't it?
なんかなあ
Yeah.
I'm glad you're back, Mr. Wild.
よく戻ってきてくれた　ワイルド君
Welcome back. And welcome back.
おかえり そして おかえりなさーい
Yeah, good to be back.
ああ ただいま
Oh, please.
あー やだ やだ
何 浮かれちゃってんのお
What's everyone getting so excited about?
え？
You didn't have to come back, you know.
別に帰ってこなくても よかったじゃん
It felt nice having one less rival to worry about.
むしろライバルが減って
やりやすかったっていうの
嘘はいけないなぁ
You shouldn't lie like that.
え？
Huh?
君が一番 ワイルド君の帰りを
心待ちにして いなかったかい？
You were looking forward to Mr. Wild's return
more than any one of us.
はあ？ どこが
Huh? N-No way...
あの人…
Every day she'd ask me, "When is Tiger coming back?"
“タイガーっていつ帰ってくんの？”
って毎日聞いてくるんですよ
あっ それ僕も聞かれた
She asked me the same thing.
俺も
Me too.
あ あ うーん
Umm...
えーっと
おかえり…
Welcome back.
ふーん
Hmm...
She's becoming quite a mess, isn't she?
面倒臭くなってきたわね　あの子
Uh-huh.
うん
まっ みんなお前を
必要としてるってことだあ
It just shows how much we missed you!
これからも頼むぞお タイガー選手
We're counting on you, Tiger!
Right...
ああ
あっ！
ああ それよりバニーは？
Oh, by the way, where's Bunny?
ん？
Were you able to tell them that you're quitting?
あんた ちゃんと辞めるって言えたの？
Actually, it didn't seem like the right time to bring it up.
あっ それが
全然言いだせる空気じゃなくって
Jeez, what are you waiting for?
もう 何やってんの
See, I wanted to tell my partner first, but he wasn't around.
しかも 最初に言おうと思っていた
相棒もいなくってさ
大丈夫なの？ こういうのは
You sure you can do this?
The longer you keep quiet,
一度言い出せないと
どんどん言いづらくなってくる…
the more difficult it'll be for you to tell them.
ああ 大丈夫　今度は絶対言えるから
Don't worry.
I'll be sure to tell them next time!
何かバニーの奴
I hear Bunny is in a really good mood today
事件の参考人に面会できるんで
今日 すげえ機嫌いいらしいんだ
from finally being able to speak to a key suspect.
Oh, yeah?
へえ
だからこのタイミングで
スコーンっとカミングアウト
I'm going to take this chance to tell him.
ならいいけど
If you say so.
早くあんたに帰ってきてもらわないと
こっちは大変なのよ
But we really need you to come back soon.
We're having a tough time here.
楓が能力出しっぱなしで
もう めちゃくちゃ
Kaede's powers have been running wild.
It's chaos.
ええ？
Huh?
家の物触ったら
ぜーんぶ壊しちゃって
She's been breaking everything in the house.
Yeah... It takes some time
ああ ハンドレッドパワーは
制御できるまで時間かかるからなあ
before you learn how to control the Hundred Power.
そうよねえ
That's right. You were the same too.
あんたの時も…
うわあっ　熱っ
Hot!
That's it!
もう ヤダッ
なーにこれ… ああー
I've had it!
あーあー　またやった
Oh no... She did it again.
もうこれじゃ しまいには
家ごと壊されちゃうかもしれないよ
If this keeps up, she might bring the whole house down!
だから あんたさ
So hurry up.
All right, already!
わかってるって
I'll send in my resignation and hurry back as soon as possible!
早くヒーロー辞めて
そっち　帰るから
ふぅ
Want some, Bunny?
どうだ バニー
あっ
Huh?
虎徹さん　戻ってたんですか？
Kotetsu, you're back?
Yeah.
ああ
で クリームとは話しできたのか？
So did you get to talk to Kriem?
それが ジェイクの死を知って
容体が悪化したそうで
No... It seems her condition worsened
after learning about Jake's death.
I see...
そっかあ
どうして ここへ
Why are you here?
Oh... Well...
ああ
ちょっと…
お前に大事な話があって
I have something important to tell you.
えっ 何ですか？
What is it?
Never mind. I'll tell you later.
あっ いやあ
まっ 後でいいよ
She wishes to talk to you, Mr. Barnaby.
バーナビーさんにお話があるそうです
あ？
Have you decided to tell me everything, Ms. Kriem?
全部 話してくれるんですね
クリームさん
ジェイクはなぜ
Why did Jake kill my parents?
僕の両親を殺したんです？
あの方は私のすべてだった
He meant everything to me.
ジェイク様だけが私の救いだった
Mister Jake was my only savior.
Hey, what are you talking about?
おい 何言ってんだ
ウッ フフッ
うっ
Ever since I was little, people treated me as if I were a monster
私は小さい頃から
ＮＥＸＴというだけで
just because I was a NEXT.
化け物のように扱われていましたの
They would vilify me wherever I went.
どこにいっても後ろ指を指された
I was persecuted by the world.
世間から虐げられていた
あの子 普通の人間じゃないんだって
I hear she's not a normal human.
ＮＥＸＴなんでしょ
She's a NEXT, right?
気持ち悪い
How creepy...
No one had anything kind to say to me.
誰も優しい言葉なんて
かけてくれなかった
Not even my parents loved me.
両親にすら…
愛されたことなんて なかったですわ
もう限界よ
I've had enough!
クリームに聞こえるだろ
Kriem can hear you.
いいのよ！　あの子のせいで
私たちまで化け物扱いされてるのよ
So what if she can?
We're being treated like monsters because of her.
このままじゃ おかしくなりそう
I'm going to go mad if this keeps up.
Why couldn't she have been born a normal child?
どうして普通の子に
生まれてくれなかったんだ
If I'd known she was a NEXT, I wouldn't have given birth to her.
ＮＥＸＴだって わかってたら
あたし… 産まなかったのに
I'm different from everyone.
私はみんなと違う
I'm not a normal human.
私は普通の人間じゃない
I look the same as everyone else, so why?
見た目は同じなのに どうして
私だけがこんな目に合うんだって
Why am I the only one being treated like this?
I was tormented by this question for such a long time.
ずっと苦しんでおりました
But then I met him.
そんな時 あの方に出会ったのです
うっ うう…
はい 騒がなーい
Don't make a fuss.
That day,
あの日
he demanded a large sum of money from my father.
あの方はお父様にたくさんのお金を
要求しましたわ
あなたは
ジェイクに誘拐されたんですか？
Jake kidnapped you?
Then why would you decide to join a guy like him?
じゃあなんで あんな男と一緒に
Mister Jake saved me.
ジェイク様は私を救ってくださったの
えっ
えーえっ
In the end, my parents didn't bring the money.
結局 時間になっても
お父様とお母様が
お金を持ってくることはなかった
They really didn't want me...
やっぱり私なんて
邪魔なだけだったんだ
私がＮＥＸＴだから
It's because I'm a NEXT...
私が普通じゃないから
It's because I'm not normal...
えぇ
お金 手に入らなくてごめんなさい
I'm sorry you couldn't get any money.
どうぞ 私を殺してください
Please go ahead and kill me.
さあ 殺してください
Kill me!
My life has no meaning.
私なんか
生きてる価値のない存在なんです
もう あたしなんて消えてしまった方が
いいんです　だから…
It would be better if I just disappeared!
So please, please...
だから…
What's wrong with not being normal?
普通じゃなくて何が悪い
Don't be ashamed. Be proud.
うなだれるな　胸を張れ
いいか　ＮＥＸＴってのは
人類が進化した究極の存在なんだ
Listen. NEXT are the ultimate form of human evolution.
We were given power because we're the chosen ones!
選ばれた人間だからこそ
能力が与えられた
えっ？ 選ばれた人間
The chosen ones?
We NEXT stand above the human race.
俺達ＮＥＸＴこそが
人類の上に立つ生物
覚えとけ
Remember that.
弱者ってのは自分より優れた存在を
認めたくねえから
The weak refuse to accept
the existence of those superior to them.
全力で否定する
お前が劣ってるからじゃねえ
You're not inferior to them.
You're superior to them,
お前が優れているから
奴らはお前を つぶそうとするんだ
and that's why they're trying to crush you.
Don't be ashamed. Be proud!
うなだれるな　胸を張れ
あっ
Go. You're free.
行けよ！　お前はもう自由だ
His words released me from my suffering.
あの方の言葉は…
私を苦しめていたものから
解放してくれた
あの方は私が生きていることを
初めて 認めてくれた存在だった
He was the first person who accepted my existence.
Wait.
待ってください
私も連れて行って
Take me with you...
あ？
Huh?
私… あなたに ついていきたい
I want to go with you!
Whatever you say...
勝手にしろ！
Now that I think about it,
今思うと
あの方と過ごした時間だけが
the only time I was happy was when I was with him.
私にとって幸せな時でした
Mister Jake and I were trying to build
私とジェイク様は
ＮＥＸＴが虐げられることのない
an ideal world ruled by NEXT,
where they would be free from persecution.
ＮＥＸＴが支配する理想郷の実現を掲げ
う… ううっ
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか？
あなたたちが邪魔さえしなければ
ＮＥＸＴは救われたのに
If you hadn't interfered, we NEXT would have been saved!
If you hadn't stopped Mister Jake,
あなた達がジェイク様をとめなければ
理想郷が完成したのに
we would have completed our ideal world!
はあ 何が理想郷だよ
How is that an "ideal world"?
その理想郷とやらじゃ
In that world, normal humans
今度は普通の人間がお前と同じ目に
合うんじゃねえのか
would just experience the same thing that you did.
迫害される側が入れ替わる
だけじゃねえのかよ
You're just becoming persecutors.
It's only natural.
それは当然ですわ
Humans are inferior to NEXT.
人間はＮＥＸＴよりも劣っている
だからって普通の人間を殺すことが
あなた達の正義なんですか
So killing normal people is your idea of justice?
ジェイクが僕の両親を殺したように
Just like the way Jake killed my parents?
In order to defend Mister Jake's honor,
ジェイク様の名誉のために
教えてあげますわ
I shall tell you something.
あの方はあなたのご両親を
He didn't kill your parents.
殺していない
あっ
Your parents were killed 21 years ago on Christmas Eve.
ご両親が殺されたのは21年前の
クリスマスイブ
私はその日に
ジェイク様に誘拐されたのよ
That was the day when Mister Jake kidnapped me.
What are you saying?
何を言っている
I was with Mister Jake on the day that happened.
事件のあったあの日
ジェイク様は私と共にいた
嘘だ
You're lying.
He didn't kill them.
あの方は犯人じゃない
Your parents' murder still hasn't been solved.
あなたの事件はまだ終わっていないのよ
You're lying!
嘘だ
I hope the past tortures you for the rest of your life!
一生 過去に苦しめられるがいいわ
あっ
This is your punishment for killing Mister Jake!
ジェイク様を殺した罰よ
What are you doing?!
おっ　お前何を
うっ うううう
Hey, hang in there.
おい しっかりしろ
What's going on here?!
何をしてるんです
私たちはウロボロスのほんの一部
We're... just a small faction of Ouroboros.
What?
Move out of the way!
どきなさい
Ouroboros will never die.
ウロボロスは終わらない
What do you mean?!
どういう意味だ
Hold that side down!
そっち押さえて！
Okay!
あああっ　ああ…
Ah... Mister Jake... I'm coming to you...
ジェイク様
あなたの…
もとに…
あ…
By the way... what did you want to tell me?
そういえば…
話って何ですか？
Huh?
え？
さっき僕に大事な話があるって…
Earlier, you said you had something important to tell me.
ああ いやっ 今じゃなくてもいいから
Oh. Well, I don't need to tell you now.
そうですか
I see.
I'm sorry, Bunny.
大丈夫か　バニー
I know you hoped this would give closure
せっかく
事件に決着がつきそうだったのに
to your parents' murder.
振り出しに戻っちまったけど
We're back to square one,
but I'm sure you'll figure it out someday.
お前だったら いずれ…
犯人はジェイクですよ
Jake is the murderer.
Huh?
え？
I still remember the murder as if it was yesterday.
今でも僕には 事件を目撃した時の
記憶が鮮明に残っています
There's no way he isn't the murderer.
奴が犯人じゃないなんてことは
ありえません
Then Kriem was making all that up?
じゃ クリームの話は全部
でまかせだってのか？
ええ
Yes.
相当僕らに
恨みを持ってたみたいですから
She must have quite the grudge against us.
But there really was a report saying
でも 実際にクリームが誘拐された
っていう届けは出てたんだぞ
that Kriem had been kidnapped.
しかも行方不明になった日は
言葉通り 21年前のクリスマスイブ
And she went missing 21 years ago
on Christmas Eve just as she said.
It doesn't prove that Jake was the one who kidnapped her.
それはジェイクが誘拐したという
証拠にはならない
いやあ だけど…
Yeah... But still...
僕の記憶の中の犯人はジェイクなんです
あの顔をはっきり覚えてるんです
I remember Jake being the murderer.
I clearly remember his face!
I remember him looking at me right after killing my parents.
父と母を殺害して振り返った
あの男の顔
I even remember he was holding a gun in his right hand,
ああ
拳銃を持つ右手に
the one with an Ouroboros tattoo on it.
ウロボロスの
タトゥーがあったことも
こんなもの見直して
どうしようっていうんですか
What's the point in looking through those?
ジェイクが手袋外してるとこ
ねえかと思って
I was wondering if there was footage of Jake with his gloves off.
え？
What?
あの事件の日
We don't know if he was with Kriem
こいつがクリームと一緒に
いたかどうかは わからない
on the day your parents were murdered.
いませんよ
He wasn't.
聞けって
Listen to me.
今 確認できることは ジェイクに
タトゥーがあったかどうかだけなんだ
What we can confirm is whether or not Jake had a tattoo.
もしもこの映像の中で
タトゥーがなかったら
If there's no tattoo in these videos...
僕の記憶が
間違ってるっていうんですか？
Are you saying that my memory is wrong?
まあ
Well...
ばかばかしい
This is stupid.
Oh!
おっ
This is it.
行くぞ
どうぞ 結果は見えてますから
Go right ahead. I already know the answer.
ヒーローが弱すぎてつまんねえって
What? Things are boring because the Heroes are too weak?
そんなお前らに朗報だ
Well, I've got some good news for you!
ちょうど折り返しの次の一戦
We'll be halfway done after the next match.
あっ
タトゥーなんてねえぞ
He doesn't have a tattoo.
It can't be!
そんな… あっ
I know. He must have had surgery to remove it.
そうか　こいつ手術か何かで
タトゥーを消したんですよ
I understand how you feel,
気持ちはわかるが
見る限りなんの跡も
but there's no sign that he ever had one.
No... Then what about my memories?
そんな…
じゃあ 僕のあの記憶は何なんだ
僕が見たあの犯人は何だったんだ
Who is the murderer I saw?
あ…
What's wrong?
どうした？
ああっ
Hey, are you all right?
おい 大丈夫か
Hey!
おい
What's going on?
どういうことだ
犯人の顔が変わった？
The murderer's face changed?
Yes.
ええ　記憶の中のジェイクの顔が
My memory of Jake's face has changed into many other faces.
いろんな人に変わっていって…
What does that mean?
何だよ　それ
That's what I want to know!
僕が聞きたいですよ
今までも そういうことあったのか
Has that ever happened before?
There was a time when I couldn't remember his face,
顔が思い出せないことは
ありましたけど
but I've never experienced anything like this.
こんなことは…
んん
ああ　もしもし
Oh, hello? How's it going?
どお？ 辞めるってちゃんと言えた？
Did you tell them you're quitting?
ああ それがまだ…
Uh... Well, not really...
What are you doing?!
何やってんの　あんたさっき
You told me earlier that you were going to tell them.
スコーンっとカミングアウトとか
言ってたじゃない
I was going to, but things came up.
そのつもり だったんだけど
もう ホントいろいろあってさ
あーんた また楓との約束破るの
Are you going to break your promise to Kaede again?
Huh?
え？
今度ばっかりはフォローできないわよ
I can't make excuses for you this time.
So how is Kaede? Has she calmed down a little?
で 楓はどお？
ちょっとは落ち着いた？
それがねえ
Well, it seems she doesn't have the same power as you.
あの子…
あんたと同じ能力じゃないみたいなのよ
あ？
What?
Her body is now acting like a magnet.
身体が磁石になる能力っていうの
Jeez!
もう
You mean...
じゃあ 楓は能力 ２つあるってこと
Kaede has two separate powers?
そんなの
あたしじゃ わからないわよ
I can't tell. That's why I want you to hurry.
だから あんたを急かしてるんでしょ
Come home already and look after her.
早く帰ってきて面倒見てあげて
Do it before something bad happens.
何かあってからじゃ遅いのよ
あー わかった
Got it.
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか
You sounded a little worried.
何か焦ってましたけど
Yeah, my daughter developed some powers.
あー ちょっと…
娘が能力に目覚めちゃって
Your daughter?
娘さんが？
Yeah.
ああ それでバニー
And there's something else I need to tell you.
お前に聞いてほしいことがあるんだ
俺 ワイルドタイガーは諸事情により
Due to certain circumstances, I, Wild Tiger...
分かりました
I understand.
え？
Huh?
You wish to leave early, right?
“早退”ですよね
Leave early?
早退？
早く娘さんの所へ行ってあげてください
Hurry up and go to your daughter.
あっいや　俺 ワイルドタイガーは
No, wait. I, Wild Tiger...
大丈夫ですよ　居なくても
It's all right. I can handle things without you.
へ？
Huh?
ご心配おかけしました
Sorry to make you worry.
あっいやいや　聞いてくれよ
Listen to me.
Hello?
もしもし
あらあ 坊ちゃんお久しぶり
Oh hello, I haven’t heard from you in a while.
え？
坊ちゃんから連絡をくださるなんて
珍しい
How unusual for you to give me a call.
あらっ そちらの方は？
Oh, who's he?
Hello, I'm Wild Tiger.
私 ワイルドタイガーです
これはこれは
Oh my.
私は坊ちゃんの家政婦をしておりました
サマンサと申します
I am Samantha.
I used to work as a housekeeper for Master Barnaby.
Hello.
どうも
サマンサおばさん
Aunt Samantha.
Yes?
はい
少しお聞きしたいことがあるんですが
There's something I want to ask you.
ええ なんでしょう
Yes, what is it?
Twenty-one years ago...
21年前 あの事件があった日
Where were you the day my parents were murdered?
あなたは どこにいたんですか？
あ？
Huh?
え？
You were not at my home that day, were you?
あの日 屋敷にはいませんでしたよね
ええ 確かあの日は風邪をこじらせて
寝込んでおりましたので
No. I believe I was in bed with a cold.
Is there anyone who can prove you were sick?
それを証明できる人は
Prove?
証明？
It was quite a long time ago.
もう だいぶ昔のことですから
では 証明はできないんですね
So you can't prove you were sick?
ちょい ちょい ちょい
Wait, wait, wait!
何ですか？
What is it?
What kind of a question is that?
お前 何聞いてんの？
さっき言いましたよね
I told you earlier that my memory of the murder's face
記憶の中で犯人の顔が
いろいろ出てきたって
changed into many other faces.
その中に彼女が…
Her face was one of them.
疑ってんのか　この人
You think she did it?!
What are you thinking, Bunny?
何考えてんだよ　バニー
こんな穏やかな おばあちゃん
つかまえて
She's such a nice old lady.
でも手がかりは これしかないんです
But this is my only lead.
All I can do right now
僕にできるのは 記憶に出てきた人を
しらみ潰しにあたるしか
is question the people who appear in my memory.
Do you think it's really wise to suspect people
そんな曖昧な記憶で
人を疑っていいと思ってんのか？
with that faulty memory of yours?
You're nuts.
お前どうかしてるぞ
あのぉ 坊ちゃん　もしもし？
Umm, Master Barnaby?
Hello?
ああ　また連絡しますんで
Oh, he'll call you back later. Sorry.
すみません
I don't know what I should do.
どうしたらいいのか わからないんです
The thing I've believed all this time
これまで信じてきたものが
突然崩れ始めて
has suddenly begun to fall apart.
僕はこれから
I don't know what I should believe anymore.
何を信じれば
I don't blame you.
そうだよな
虎徹さん
Kotetsu...
ん？
僕はヒーローを
辞めた方が いいのかもしれない
Maybe it's best that I quit being a Hero.
Huh?
え？
こんな混乱した状態の中で
ヒーローを続けていく自信がありません
I'm not confident I can be a Hero in my confused state.
What?!
はああ？
Wait, wait, wait!
あっ いやいやいやー
すみません
一晩考えさせてください
I'm sorry. Let me think about it tonight.
Wait.
ちょっと
Hey!
うわぁ ああ…
ごめんって　楓
Sorry, Kaede.
いやもうホントに大変だったんだよ
Daddy's having a really tough time here!
パパが辞めるって言おうとしたら
パパの友達が辞めたいって言いだしてさ
Just when Daddy was about to say he's going to quit,
Daddy's friend says that he wants to quit!
だから？
So?
Well... You see...
いやあ だからさ
It's difficult to say that Daddy's quitting in that situation.
そんな状況じゃあ
パパが辞めるって言いづらいだろ
で 帰れなくなったと
So you're saying you can't come back?
あー わかってくれた？
Do you understand?
そんな言い訳信じるか！
I'm not buying that excuse!
I-It's not an excuse.
言い訳じゃなくて
Oh, how are your powers?
あっ 能力はどうだ
２つも持ってるなんてすごいよな
I hear you have two. That's amazing.
いやっ １つだから
No, I only have one.
え？
Huh?
I have one power!
能力は１つ
But Grandma said that
いやでも
磁石の能力とハンドレッドパワーだって
おばあちゃんが
you had that magnetic power and the Hundred Power.
私の能力ってコピーなんだって
I have the ability to copy powers.
コピー？
Copy?
ＮＥＸＴの能力 持ってる人に触ると
Uncle Muramasa said that
自動的に能力をコピーしちゃうって
I automatically copy the power of any NEXT I touch.
村正おじちゃんが言ってた
そんな能力初めて聞いたな
I've never heard of such power.
What?
ええ？
So does the previous power go away when you copy a new one?
それはコピーしたら前の能力は
消えるのか
I don't know.
わかんない わかんない
ってか 説明すんの面倒くさい
And I don't even want to talk about it.
そんなあ　パパにも教えてくれよ
Oh, come on. Please tell Daddy.
お父さんに話しても意味ないじゃん
What's the point in talking to you, Dad?
だって帰ってこないんだから
You're not even coming back.
いやあ だから明日 必ず
No, I'll definitely come home tomorrow.
楓〜
Kaede...
灰色に染まる街の片隅で
hai iro ni somaru machi no katasumi de souzou dake no yume wo miteita
In an obscure corner of the ashen city, I was having a surreal dream.
想像だけの夢をみていた
存在する事の意味を
sonzai suru koto no imi wo nantonaku kangaehajimeta
I started to think about the meaning of existence.
なんとなく考え始めた
But I never know
BUT, I NEVER KNOW.
But, I never know.
myself＆夢＆
MYSELF AND yume AND TRUE AND ANYMORE
Myself & dreams & truth & anymore.
true＆Anymore
もう… もっと…
mou... motto...
At all...
こんな世界で私に聞いたの
konna sekai de watashi ni kita no ittai nani ga dekiru no ka wo
I asked myself what one can do in a world like this.
一体何が出来るのかを
あなたの笑顔が教えてくれたような
anata no egao ga oshiete kureta youna sonna kigashita kara
And I felt that your smiling face could teach me the answer.
そんな気がしたから
光を見つけたような
hikari wo mitsuketa youna itami ni furerareru
And enabled me to be touched by the pain of finding light.
痛みに触れられる
そう そんな気がした
sou, sonna kigashita
Yes, that was the feeling.
人は皆儚い夢を
hito wa mina hakanai yume wo kono te ni ireru tame ni
In pursuing their fleeting dreams,
この手に入れる為に
永遠の真実さえ見失う
eien no shinjitsu sae miushinau
people lose sight of the eternal truth.
消えない悲しい明日に
kienai kanashii asu ni hikari wo kureta no wa daredemo naku tatta hitori
No one made me realize that there is a light that never dims but you,
光をくれたのは
誰でもなく たった一人
過去も未来も
shinjitai
I want to believe.
kako mo mirai mo wakachiaeru zutto
always sharing the past and the future.
分かち合えるずっと
ああっ
わあああ…
ども TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
夢に出てきた女優さんは
好きになっちゃうほう　虎徹です
Hi! I'm Kotetsu, the member of Tiger & Bunny
who ends up liking actresses who appear in his dreams!
ウロボロスの真相は
再び闇の中
The truth about Ouroboros is a complete mystery again.
でも俺はもうヒーローを…
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
But I've already decided to quit being a Hero...
ゼアーズ ノウ ウェイ アウト
Next time on Tiger & Bunny:
えっこれ合ってる？
Am I saying this correctly?